Guide to the Raymond C. Battalio and John B. Van Huyck Papers, 1949-2014, bulk 1972-2014 RL.11714
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Experiments, 1986-2013
  - Average Opinion Games, 1988-2006
    - Beauty Contest (BB1) Electronic Files, 1999-2001; 153 files; approximately 8 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0045)
      Text, image, and executable files.
    - Commodity Market Games, 1994 and undated; 10 folders (Box 35)
      Participant response sheets, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - PG2, 1999-2001; undated; 18 folders (Box 35)
      Handouts, questionnaires, participant instructions, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - PG3, 2006 (Box 35)
      Questionnaires, sample responses, and statistical analyses.
    - PG3 Electronic Files, 2000-2006; 611 files; approximately 14 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0008, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0042, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0044)
      Materials restricted due to sensitive content. Some electronic files in RL11714-SET-0008 contain personally identifiable information (PII) that has not been redacted. Contact Research Services for more information.
  - Chaos, 1991-1995
    Files for experiments on chaotic dynamics, with modifications examining probabilistic matching of participants, zero information, and forecasting. Arranged alphabetically by experiment.
    - Chaos, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 36)
      Questionnaires.
    - Chaos Experiments Electronic Files, 1991-1993; 313 files; approximately 9 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Dataset, text, executable, and backup files.
    - Chaos: Stable/Seven Cycle, 1991; 7 folders (Box 36)
      Participant instructions, questionnaires, and experiment data.
    - Chaos (NOINF, PRBMAT), 1995; 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Chaos (NOINF, PRBMAT) Electronic Files, 1995; 66 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text and backup files.
    - Chaos (NOINF), 1994; 2 folders (Box 36)
      Experiment data, statistical analyses, and notes.
    - Chaos/FORE2: Selection Dynamics, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 36)
      Participant instructions and experiment data.
    - Chaos/FORE2 Electronic Files, 1987-2001; 856 files; approximately 20 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, dataset, executable, and backup files.
    - Forecasting (FORE2), 1992 (Box 36)
    - Forecasting (FORE2) Electronic Files, 1987-1992; 222 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 67, Disk RL11714-FL3-0234, Disk RL11714-FL3-0235)
  - Conventions, 1990-2013
    Files for experiments on the emergence of conventions. Several vintages of these experiments were conducted with multiple extensions. In some cases, there is apparent overlap between experiments on the emergence of conventions and coordination experiments. Arranged alphabetically by experiment.
    - C2, 1995-1996; 6 folders (Box 38)
    - C2 Electronics Files, 1995-1996; 64 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 71, Disk RL11714-FL3-0625, Disk RL11714-FL3-0634, Box 72, Disk RL11714-FL3-0751)
      Text and dataset files; zipped folders.
    - C3: Stag Hunt Games, 1995 and undated; 3 folders (Box 38)
      Participant instructions, response forms, questionnaires, and experiment data.
    - C3: Stag Hunt Games Electronic Files, 1994-1998; 161 files; approximately 7 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, image, dataset, and executable files.
    - C4 (1-3 of 7), 1996-1998; 3 folders (Box 38)
      Participant instructions, response forms, and experiment data.
    - C4 (4-7 of 7), undated; 4 folders (Box 64)
      Participant instructions.
    - C4 Electronic Files, 1993-1999; 1,542 files; approximately 68 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, executable, image, dataset, and backup files.
    - C4: PD, 1997-1998; 3 folders (Box 38)
    - C4: PD Electronic Files, 1993-1998; 1,018 files; approximately 49 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0049)
      Text, image, executable, dataset, and backup files.
    - C4: Stag Hunt Experiments with Larry Samuelson, 1996; 6 folders (Box 38)
      Experiment results, statistical analyses, and correspondence.
    - C4: Stag Hunt Games, 1997-1999 (Box 38)
    - C6, 1997-1998 and undated; 8 folders (Box 39)
      Participant instructions, questionnaires, response forms, and experiment data.
    - C6 Electronic Files, 1990-1998; 2,013 files; approximately 86 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, executable, image, and dataset files.
    - C7: Coordination, Community, and Convention, 1996-2004; 2 folders (Box 39)
      Research outline, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - C8, 1998-2001 and undated; 5 folders (Box 39)
      Participant instructions, questionnaires, experiment data, and notes.
    - C8 Electronic Files, 1993-2001; 1,338 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - C8: Aspirations versus Optimization Incentives, 1999 (Box 39)
      Statistical analyses.
    - C8: Random Order Statistic, 1998 (Box 39)
      Experiment design notes, experiment data, and correspondence for experiments run in collaboration with David Cooper.
    - C9 (1-5 of 15), 1998-2001; 5 folders (Box 39)
      Participant instructions, response forms, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - C9 (6-14 of 15), 2000-2001; 9 folders (Box 40)
      Participant instructions, response forms, statistical analyses, and research material.
    - C9 (15 of 15), undated (Box 64)
      Participant instructions and response sheets.
    - C9 Electronic Files, 1993-2001; 1,189 files; approximately 248 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0008)
      Text, spreadasheet, executable, dataset, and image files.
    - C9: Similarity, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 40)
    - C9: Version 8 (1-9 of 14), 2000-2001 and undated; 9 folders (Box 40)
      Participant response forms, experiment data, statistical analyses, and research material.
    - C9: Version 8 (10-14 of 14), 1998-2001; 5 folders (Box 41)
      Experiment data, statistical analysis, and research material.
    - CONV2, 1990-1992; 14 folders (Box 37)
    - CONV2 Electronic Files, 1992-1996; 1,490 files; approximately 39 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, executable, and dataset files.
    - Conventions (1-13 of 16), 1990-1995; 13 folders (Box 36)
    - Conventions (14-16 of 16), 1992; 3 folders (Box 37)
      Questionnaires, response forms, and experiment data.
    - Conventions Data Disk (C1), 1990-1992 (Box 36)
    - Conventions Data Disk (C1) Electronic Files, 1991-1993; 11 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 72, Disk RL11714-FL3-0749, Disk RL11714-FL3-0750)
    - Conventions Experiments Audiocassettes, 1992-1993
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX, Session 5, 1992 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0021)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1, Session 7, 1992 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0026)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1, Session 9, 1992 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0027)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1, Session 11, 1992 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0023)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1 RPM-I, Session 1, 1993 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0028)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1 RPM-I, Session 4, 1993 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0029)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1 RPM-S, Session 4, 1993 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0019)
      - Original Audiocassette, MATRIX1 RPM-T, Session 3, 1993 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0024)
      - Original Audiocassette, [blank], undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0020)
      - Original Audiocassette, [blank], undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0022)
    - Conventions Experiments Electronic Files, 1989-2004; 13,949 files; approximately 3.3 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0008)
      Text, audio, image, spreadsheet, dataset, executable, and backup files; zipped folders.
    - Conventions: Figures, 1992 and undated; 3 folders (Box 37)
      Drafts of figures and data used in publications.
    - Conventions: Linear Dynamic, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 38)
      Note and experiment data.
    - Evolution of Conventions, 1990-1991; 3 folders (Box 37)
      Experiment data and experiment design notes.
    - Measuring Social Preferences (C9), 1998-2008; 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Stag Hunt Games, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Stag Hunt Games (R1), 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 41)
      Statistical analyses for stag hunt games with rule learning.
  - Coordination, 1987-2001
    Access note. Some materials are fragile audiov formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
    Files for experiments on coordination games. Several vintages of these experiments were conducted with multiple extensions. In some cases, there is apparent overlap between coordination experiments and experiments on the emergence of conventions. Arranged alphabetically by experiment.
    - Bluebox 1-4 (CRAW 1-4), undated; 4 folders (Box 41)
    - Bluebox 1-4 (CRAW 1-4) Electronic Files, 1990-1995; 142 files; approximately 32 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, dataset, and executable files.
    - Coordination Experiments Audiocassettes, 1993-1995
      - Original Audiocassette, CR2_1404, 1993 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0012)
      - Original Audiocassette, CR4, Assign3, Session 15, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0015)
      - Original Audiocassette, CRAW4, Assign4, 1995 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0018)
      - Original Audiocassette, CRAW4, Session 16, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0016)
      - Original Audiocassette, CRAW4, Session 17, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0017)
      - Original Audiocassette, [blank], undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0013)
      - Original Audiocassette, [blank], undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0014)
    - Coordination Experiments Electronic Files, 1990-1995; 483 files; approximately 32 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Coordination Games (1-12 of 155), 1987-1988; 12 folders (Box 41)
      Participant instructions and response sheets and booklets.
    - Coordination Games (13-30 of 155), 1988-1994 and undated; 18 folders (Box 42)
      Participant instructions, response sheets and booklets, and experiment data.
    - Coordination Games (31-47 of 155), 1988 and undated; 17 folders (Box 43)
    - Coordination Games (48-73 of 155), 1988 and undated; 26 folders (Box 44)
    - Coordination Games (74-102 of 155), 1987-1991 and undated; 29 folders (Box 45)
      Participant instructions, response sheets and booklets, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - Coordination Games (103-118 of 155), 1990-1992 and undated; 16 folders (Box 46)
      Participant instructions and response booklets.
    - Coordination Games (119-132 of 155), 1990-1992; 14 folders (Box 47)
    - Coordination Games (133-149 of 155), 1990-1992; 17 folders (Box 48)
      Participant instructions, response booklets and forms, and experiment data.
    - Coordination Games (150-154 of 155), 1990-1992; 5 folders (Box 49)
      Response booklets and experiment data.
    - Coordination Games (155 of 155), 1997 (Box 49)
      Questionnaires and instructions for using experiment computer system.
    - Coordination Games (RPS), 1988-1994 and undated; 4 folders (Box 49)
      Participant instructions, response forms, and statistical analyses.
    - Coordination Games (RPS) Electronic Files, 1994-1995; 10 files; approximately 3 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Dataset files.
    - CR1, 1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 50)
      Participant instructions and questionnaires.
    - CR3, 1999-2001 (Box 50)
      Experiment data and participant instructions.
    - CR3 Electronic Files, 1992-2001; 434 files; approximately 33 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - CR4: No Information Games (1-3 of 5), 1994; 3 folders (Box 50)
    - CR4: No Information Games (4-5 of 5), 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - CR4 Electronic Files, 1994-1995; 471 files; approximately 20 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - CRAW1, 1992-1993; 6 folders (Box 49)
      Participant instructions, response forms, and experiment data for experiments conducted with Bill Rankin.
    - CRAW2, undated (Box 50)
      Participant instructions and response forms.
    - CRAW3, undated (Box 50)
    - CRAW3/CRAW4, 1993 (Box 50)
      Experiment data.
    - CRAW3/CRAW4 Electronic Files, 1992-1995; 852 files; approximately 78 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - CRAW4, 1993-1995 and undated; 7 folders (Box 50)
      Participant instructions, response forms, and experiment data for experiments conducted with Beth Seely.
    - CRAW4 Electronic Files, 1992-1996; 70 files; approximately 12 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - CRAWFORD1, 1992; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - CRAWFORD1 Electronic Files, 1990-1993; 568 files; approximately 53 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - CRAWFORD2, 1993 (Box 50)
    - CRAWFORD2 Electronic Files, 1992-1998; 310 files; approximately 38 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - CRAWFORD3, undated (Box 50)
      Experiment system instructions.
    - CRAWFORD4, undated (Box 50)
    - Credible Assignments (1-19 of 37), 1988-1989 and undated; 19 folders (Box 55)
    - Credible Assignments (20-31 of 37), undated; 12 folders (Box 56)
      Response forms.
    - Credible Assignments (32-37 of 37), undated; 6 folders (Box 57)
    - Hawk-Dove Games (CRAW4), 1995; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Hawk-Dove Games (CRAW4) Electronic Files, 1993-1995; 171 files; approximately 12 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Notes on Coordination Games, 1987 (Box 64)
      Experiment design notes.
  - Decentralized Allocation, 1979-2006
    Files for experiments on decentralized allocation, including allocation in markets and the role of historical information in market experiments. Arranged alphabetically by experiment.
    - Decentralized Allocation, 1987-1989 and undated; 10 folders (Box 51)
      Participant instructions, response forms, experiment data, and research notes.
    - Decentralized Allocation Experiments Electronic Files, 1995-2003; 589 files; approximately 369 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0008, Box 73, Disk RL11714-FL3-0926, Box 77, Disk RL11714-FL5-0001, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0167)
    - DECX1, 1989-1990; undated; 5 folders (Box 51)
      Notes, readings, and experiment data.
    - DECX2, undated; 3 folders (Box 51)
    - DECX2 Electronic Files, 1988-1996; 782 files; approximately 36 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - DX2, undated; 5 folders (Box 51)
      Response forms and experiment data.
    - DX2 Electronic Files, 2003; 422 files; approximately 18 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0063)
    - DX2: Market Games, 1988-1996 (Box 51)
      Experiment design notes, experiment data, participant instructions, and sample response sheets.
    - DX2: Market Price Dispersion, 2004-2006; 2 folders (Box 51)
      Research notes, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - DX2: Sequential Pot Experiments, 1996; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - DX3, 2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box 51)
      Research notes.
    - DX3 Electronic Files, 2004; 630 files; approximately 9 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0065)
  - Peasant-Dictator, 1989-2013
    Files for experiments in which participants decide how much to produce (peasants) and how much to tax production (dictators) so that the emergence of norms and conventions can be studied. Arranged alphabetically by experiment.
    - Commitment vs Discretion (PD1), 1992 and undated; 6 folders (Box 52)
    - PD1, 1992-1994; 11 folders (Box 52)
    - PD1 Electronic Files, 1991-1992; 2,469 files; approximately 90 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - PD1: Ray's Analysis, 1994 and undated; 3 folders (Box 52)
      Printouts of code and draft charts and tables for analysis.
    - PD2, 1992-1993; 4 folders (Box 52)
    - PD2 Electronic Files, 1992-1993; 814 files; approximately 30 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Peasant-Dictator Games, 1994-1996; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - Peasant-Dictator Games Audiocassettes, 1992
      - Original Audiocassette, EXPPD1.SO1, 1992 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0006)
      - Original Audiocassette, Rep01.ALL, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0008)
      - Original Audiocassette, Rep02.PD2, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0009)
      - Original Audiocassette, Rep03.ALL, 1992 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0010)
      - Original Audiocassette, Rep04.PD2 and Rep06.PD2, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0011)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 2 and 3, 1992 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0007)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 6 and 7, PD1, 1992 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0025)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 10 and 11, 1992 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0001)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 12 and 13, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0002)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 14, 1992 (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0003)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 21, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0004)
      - Original Audiocassette, Session 22, undated (Box 78, Audio-cassette RL11714-CS-0005)
    - Peasant-Dictator Games Electronic Files, 1989-1996; 1,849 files; approximately 86 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, executable, and dataset files; zipped folder.
    - Peasant-Dictator Games Reporting Sheets, 2012-2013 and undated; 36 folders (Box 53)
      Response sheets for different roles played in peasant-dictator games.
    - Peasant-Dictator Games: Battalio Files, 1991-1992; 7 folders (Box 54)
      Experiment data and preliminary analyses for "commitment versus discretion" and "reputation" variations of peasant-dictator games from Battalio's files.
    - Reputation (PD0, PD2), 1992-1996 and undated; 10 folders (Box 54)
      Experiment data, statistical analyses, and participant instructions.
    - Reputation (PD0, PD2) Electronic Files, 1992-1993; 406 files; approximately 15 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
  - Other Experiments and Related Materials, 1985-2013
    Files for experiments that could not reliably be linked to other types. These experiments include random order statistics, games of Nim, and sequential bargaining, among others. Also included are relevant files on software used to conduct experiments and statistically analyize results. Arranged alphabetically by experiment.
    - Adaptive Behavior, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Bargaining (RPS, MATRIX2), 1994; 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Bargaining (RPS, MATRIX2) Electronic Files, 1990-1994; 11 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 71, Disk RL11714-FL3-0630, Disk RL11714-FL3-0632)
    - Consent Form Sample, undated (Box 64)
    - Economics Research Lab (ERL) Demo, undated (Box 54)
    - ERL Source Code, undated; 3 folders (Box 57)
      For different experiments deployed using ERL software.
    - Eureka Learning, 2008 (Box 57)
      Draft figures and tables for experiments on learning behavior.
    - Evidence on Repeated Dominance Solvable Games, 1992-1994; 3 folders (Box 57)
    - Experiment Results for Revealed Preferences, undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Freeway Experiment, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
      Notes and experiment data.
    - Friedman's Norm, 1995 (Box 57)
    - FRS1: Quadratic Specification, 1987; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - FRS6: Data, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Global Games, 2013 and undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
      Questionnaires and experiment data.
    - Half-the-Mean-Game, 1989 (Box 57)
      Notes and response sheets.
    - HvM Nim, undated; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - HvM Electronic Files, 2000; 31 files; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0067)
      Image, spreadsheet, text, and executable files.
    - Institutional Choice Experiments, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 58)
      Experiment data and preliminary writings.
    - Institutional Choice Experiments Electronic Files, 1989-1992; 51 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 66, Disk RL11714-FL3-0003, Disk RL11714-FL3-0004)
    - Label, No Label Experiments, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Liminf, 1994-1995 (Box 58)
    - Liminf Electronic Files, 1994-1995; 21 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Dataset and executable files.
    - Market Games, undated; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Mathematica Packages, undated (Box 64)
      Printout of custom packages used for analyzing experiments.
    - MATRIX1, 1992-1994; 9 folders (Box 58)
      Participant instructions, response sheets, experiment data, and material related to experiment software.
    - MATRIX1 Electronic Files, 1992-1993; 1,796 files; approximately 46 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, executable, dataset, and backup files.
    - Min Rule with Monitoring, 1988; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous Results, undated (Box 58)
    - Nim, 2000-2005 and undated; 6 folders (Box 58)
    - Nim Electronic Files, 1998-2005; 375 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0051, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0057, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0058)
      Spreadsheet, text, image, and executable files.
    - Nim6, 2010 (Box 59)
      Notes and experiment results.
    - NimRR, 1999-2000 and undated; 4 folders (Box 59)
      Notes, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - NimRR Electronic Files, 1998-2000; 97 files; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0038)
      Text, spreadsheet, executable, and image files.
    - No Information Games (OS), 1994-1995; 4 folders (Box 59)
    - No Information Games (OS) Electronic Files, 1994; 6 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 66, Disk RL11714-FL3-0009, Disk RL11714-FL3-0010)
      Executable files.
    - Order Statistic Games (OS), 1992-1995; 4 folders (Box 59)
      Experiment design notes, response sheets, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - Order Statistic Games (OS10), 1993-2000; 8 folders (Box 59)
      Participant instructions, questionnaires, response sheets, experiment data, and statistical analyses.
    - Order Statistic Games (OS10) Electronic Files, 1993-1998; 1,316 files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Order Statistic Games (OS5, OS7), 1990-1996; 2 folders (Box 59)
      Participant instructions, experiment data, notes, and statistical analyses.
    - Order Statistic Games (OS6), 1992-1995; 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Other Experiments and Related Materials Electronic Files, 1985-2009; 82,943 files; approximately 10.1 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text, image, executable, dataset, spreadsheet, audio, backup, and aggregate files; zipped folders.
      RL11714-OP-0168 and 0169 include version 2.0.16 and 2.1.4 of z-Tree, a "widely used software package for developing and carrying out economic experiments."